and in Gudermes, those who
а у вас вот в Гудермесе вот те которые
died were from Gudermes, are there somewhere
погибли родом из Гудермеса они где-то
such a cemetery for the military or whoever is
есть такое кладбище для военных или кого
buried somewhere, I'll tell you honestly And when
где хоронят вот теб честно скажу А как
the war started, not a single person who died
война началась ни один погибший
was in Gudermes, how is it that in
был как это так получается что э в
every city in Russia  there is a dead person in
каждом городе России есть погибший в
Gudermes there are no dead people in Gudermes there is
Гудермесе нет погибших в Гудермесе нету
not
не
one I mean it turns out that
один В смысле так получается это что
Russians
русские
die at funerals I was not
умирают на похоронах Не был
[laughter]
[смех]
I am a
я
crowbar Shalom Where are you from
Шалом Вы откуда
Sheriff
Шериф
[laughter]
[смех]
Chechnya Good joke good
Чечня Хорошая шутка хорошая
what really che Well show me the badge it is an
что реально чи А ну покажи значок это
eight-pointed Akhmatova lishi  Yes, exactly
восьмиконечный ахматовский лиши Да точно
there Kadyrov
там Кадыров
is cool Akhmat Kadyrov is the second Who is
прикольно Ахмат Кадырова второй Кто
there and I don’t know pos and his son
там и я не знаю пос а сыночек его
Yes Ramzanka Yakh matka is cool where I’m from I’m
Да рамзанка Ях матка прикольно откуда Я
from Shati I’m from Ingushetia But now I live in
из шати я из Ингушетии Но живу сейчас в
California I’m from
Калифорнии Я из
Magas oh great
магаса о здоро
Mar joke yes Good yes passed I’m just a
Мар шутка да Хорош да прошла я прям
spitting image of Ingush  just like you are a spitting image of a
вылитый Ингуш так же как ты вылитый
Chechen Ukrainian No,
чеченец украинец Да
I am not  russ Belarusian and
нет я русс Белорус а
russ himself is from Rostov But I live in
русс сам родом из Ростова Но живу в
California
Калифорнии
pure Russian and a little bit of you
чистый русский да чуть-чуть у тебя Ну
Well, I have relatives
как бы у меня родственники
from Krasnodar Krai there are Cossacks And
с Краснодарского края там есть казаки А
there are Yes there are some Circassians So
есть Да есть кто-то из черкесов Так что
I don't know completely That's why yes I  well, you can see
я не знаю полностью Поэтому да я ж видно
the dark-haired
чернявый
one understood how it is in Grozny or where are
такой понял как там у вас в Грозном или
you
вы
from Gudermes, the city of RME It's
откуда Гудермес город рме
cool I have a friend there, Akhmet
Прикольно у меня там знакомый есть Ахмет
from
из
Gudermes, yes, yes, I'm
Гудермеса есть да Да я
all about
все
Yame, of course, a lot, yes, and he was also on chat roulette, I
Яме конечно много да а он в чат рулетке
saw him there, I met him
тоже был там видел его познакомился
today, no, no  today he was with the
сегодня Да не не сегодня вообще был он с
flag of the Ichkerian
флагом ичкерийского
house about flew in Yes yes yes houses houses
дома о налетела Да да да дома дома
houses And what do you have there already I saw
дома А что там у вас уже Я видел до
drones fly to Grozny to Gudermes
Грозного до Гудермеса долетают дроны
Yes I didn't see RME drones honestly go well there he
Да я не видел рме дроны честно го ну там
also flew to this special forces university
улетел тоже в этот университет спецназа
this is Gudermes Well  I have friends working there
это ж гудермесс Ну у меня там друзья
Well, they say last month there was a visit There was
Ну они говорят прошлый месяц был прит
an arrival at the Gudermes Special Forces University
Был Прилёт в университет спецназа
Yes, there was
Гудермес Да был
an arrival They said
прилёт говорили
well, a lot of people work there right here  next to this
ну там работают много здесь же рядом это
I didn't hear anything and I asked I don't know
я ничего не слышал и я спросил Не знаю
where she is at And what are you looking for in the chat roulette
куда она при А что ищете в чат рулетке
here I have clients for
тут я клиентов
yourself you want to find a client on the
себе вы в щт рулетке хотите клиента на
hat in Gudermes in the chat roulette
шапке в Гудермесе найти
Yes, I wonder And what brands do you have there I
Да интересно А у вас какие там бренды Я
understand I'm looking at what's completely there  no, these are
так понял смотрю что там совсем не это
not Russian BNDs, I have r guns,
не русские бнд не у меня есть р гу ны
I have hats, too, also earflaps,
есть у меня шапки тоже также ушанки
Afghans. And in Russia now it is patriotic
афганки А в России сейчас патриотично
to sell
продавать
Louis Vuitton
луивитон
Louis Vuitton Well, this is this, let's say Gucci,
луивитон Ну это вот это скажем Gucci
about last year in the summer, let's say
примерно в прошлом году летом скажем
it was good, then it stopped,
хорошо она шла потом остановилась
it's been almost 20 years. I  I work Gucci this is how it
вот почти 20 лет Я работаю Gucci вот так
works sometimes it is in use sometimes
работает то в ходу она бывает то вообще
no one needs it at all And Gucci itself is a
никому не нужна А сама Gucci это вообще
powerful brand of course And where do they
мощный бренд конечно А откуда сейчас в
bring these Guccis to Russia now if there are sanctions
Россию привозят эти Gucci если санкции
Well from China and the originals They probably won't even
Ну с Китая а оригиналы Здесь даже не
understand here I don't know And so this is
поймут наверно не знаю А так это вас
official for you  you are not selling originals yes yes it is
официально не оригиналами торгуете да да
not original it is expensive and these are the
не оригинал он же дорого же стоит а это
people who buy it they know that it is
люди которые покупают они знают что это
not original yes Well of course they know if
не оригинал да Ну конечно знают если вот
for example I have Gucci Luxo  Lux copy
примерно у меня Gucci люксо Люкс копия
original in China which is made it
оригинал в Китае которая сделана она
costs here 00 rubles
стоит здесь 00 руб
well 15 dollars and the originals they are specifically
ну 15 долларов а оригиналы они конкретно
expensive interestingly from
дорогие интересно с
150 euros These are approximately the prices of the
150 евро Вот примерно вот такие расценки
original Yes I understand otherwise I think these are all
оригина Да я понял а то я думаю это все
original Gucci I think someone
оригинальные Gucci думаю ктото так
buys Good not here I have  original
покупает Гуд не здесь У меня оригинал
only here Korean caps NB
только вот здесь корейские кепки NB
76 the rest are all China e Kyrgyzstan
76 остальные всё Китай э Киргизия
Kyrgyzstan Well yes there is cotton there cotton
Киргизстан Ну да там хлопок хлопок есть
because I know there is production
потому что я знаю там производство
by the way in Kyrgyzstan here is the Dordoi market
кстати в Киргизии вот Дордой рынок
Bishkek a powerful market in Central Asia
бишкеки мощный рынок на среднем Азии
actually there is no such market there is a
вообще то такого рынка нету там вообще
big market there really
большой рынок очень
well they  they carry goods from Korea from Turkey from
ну они возят товары с Кореи с Турции с
China
Китая
Anya and you are a
Аня а вы
Muslim Yes of course It's just that I
мусульманин Да конечно Просто я
have seen most Muslims They don't have a moustache
большинство мусульман видел Они без усов
They have a beard but no
они с бородой но без
moustache I just trim my moustache here is the
усов Я просто подстригаю усы вот здесь
upper lip Yeah I thought so Well this is
верхняя губа есть Ага я так думал Ну это
someone like a Chechen  just
кто-то как бы под чеченца просто
copies but with a moustache I got it Yeah, not
копирует но с усами понял Угу не вот
like that, our people wear moustaches,
так-то у нас усы носят люди
uh, and before that too, here are the heroes, let's say
ээ и раньше тоже начи вот герои скажем
Baysangur  Sheikh Manr was and Dudai
там байсангур Шейх манр был да и дудай
too all with a moustache Yes with a
тоже все усами Да
moustache they just need to shorten
усами были просто здесь надо укорачивать
them here you can't take them off completely
их полностью снимать
under the
под
sign of
зна
Kores many Muslims they have a moustache Swat will
корес многие мусульмане они ус Сват
turn out it is said that they
получатся сказано ди что
strongly follow strongly shorten
сильно следуют сильно укорачивают
Yes here we have a theme with a moustache - this is
Да здесь у нас тема усами - это
generally specific And what
вообще конкретно А что
exactly Well  Some don't like it, let's say
именно Ну Некоторым не нравится скажем
75 80%, some
75 80% некоторым
like it. And you've been living in America for a long time,
нравится вот А ты давно живёшь в Америке
well, 18 years, in 2 years, the twentieth,
ну 18 лет через 2 года двадцатое
first as a student, and then you entered
сначала студентом а потом Поступил в
graduate school, then defended your dissertation and
аспирантуру потом защитил диссертацию и
received citizenship, you're already a citizen. By the way,
получил гражданин ты уже Да тут кстати
we have a lot of people here from Chechnya and Ingushetia.
много у нас есть из Чечни из Ингушетии
there are in this here
есть в это вот
I am yes there are Chechens there yes In ka there are
я да чеченцы есть там да В ка там есть
Chechens even earlier who
чеченцы даже раньше которые
when the second world
когда второ мирово
war was yes yes well in short You know what yes
война была да да ну короче Знаешь что да
you understand Cool And how are you there now
понимаешь Прикольно А как там вас сейчас
calm and there now calm with you in
спокойно а там сейчас спокойно у вас в
Chechnya Yes in general calm
Чечне Да вообще спокойно
here  very calmly Because I'm
здесь очень даже спокойно Потому что я
not here plane when Well here which
не вот самолёт когда Ну тут который
beat up that fell in this in Kazakhstan they
избили что упал в этом в Казахстане то
also say that  now nothing flies
же говорят что теперь не летает ничего
Yes in Grozny from
Да в грозной изза
abroad
границы
they fly to Turkey I
зани Турции летают я точно
know for sure Turkey flies to Moscow they fly
знаю Турцию летают е куда Москву летают
but
а вот
Kyrgyzstan also
Киргизию тоже
flies here Kazakhstan
летают вот Казахстан
and for example your
а у Вас например
women are now walking Well they are with their
женщины сейчас ходят Ну они с закрытыми
faces covered or can they walk without their faces covered what
лицами или можно без закрытых ходить что
I heard with their faces covered  no they walk around with
я слышал закрытыми лицами нет ходят
their faces covered because it's
закрытыми лицами потому что это вот
somewhere there in Syria Well even in Syria in
где-то там в Сирии Ну даже в Сирии в
principle it seems to be open there are
принципе вроде открыты есть
Muslim countries where they cover their faces
мусульманские страны где закрывают лица
and
да
women in Syria Egypt there Saudi
женщин в Сирии Египет там Саудовской
Arabia there you meet of course a
Аравии там встречаешь конечно
kid who is so
дит который так
cool And how many do you have in
прикольно А сколько вот у вас в день
there is a buyers day Well now it's January it's like a dead
есть Ну сейчас январь он как бы Мёртвый
season
сезон считается
January in February we are already preparing Well for the
январь в феврале уже мы готовимся Ну
summer season there are caps Panamas Rashki
летнему сезону там кепки Панамы рашки
here with us this has
вот у нас вот это поменялось
completely changed the weather has changed with us And what
полностью погода поменялась у нас А что
happened to the
случилось с
weather there
погодой снега
is no snow Where did
нету А куда
it go And how are you  there with snow here in
делся А у вас как там со снегом у нас в
California there is no snow at all And yes
Калифорнии снега не бывает вообще А да у
here in winter p7 p8
нас зимой п7 п8
what about in summer it will be really hot in summer
что се летом-то вообще жарко будет летом
in shorts  we just go to the beach girls
в шортиках ходим просто девочки пляжа
it's just bomb Simo Well it's like
это просто бомби Симо Ну это как у ва у
you people how do you feel about the fact that
вас люди как типа относятся к тому что
now there is a war between Russia and
сейчас Война идёт между Россией и
Ukraine Well war in any
Украиной Ну война в любом
case no one supports
случае никто не поддерживает
war civilians suffer and so all
войну страдают мирные люди а так все
people are not politicians what are they  it
люди же не политики они
happens as it happens Yes but
что происходит как происходит Да но
many many I know many guys from Chechnya
много много я знаю много парней из Чечни
go to fight it turns out contract soldiers
идут воевать получается контрактникам
sign up go to die for money
подписывают идут за деньги
Well this is war it
умирать Ну это война по-разному
happens in different ways warriors are
бывает воины
different they happen someone from
же по-разному они бывает кто-то с
America probably goes there to fight in
Америки наверное идёт туда воевать по
Contra Yes there are such  yes And in
Контра Да есть такие да А у вас вот в
Gudermes, those who died were
Гудермесе вот те которые погибли родом
from Gudermes, do they have a
из Гудермеса они где-то есть такое
cemetery somewhere for the military or whoever is
кладбище для военных или кого где
buried there? I'll tell you honestly, when the war
хоронят Вот тебе честно скажу как война
started, not a single person died in the RME,
началась ни один погибший в рме не
how is it that in every
было как это так получается что в каждом
city in Russia  there are dead in Gudermes
городе России есть погибшие в Гудермес
there are no dead in Gudermes there is not
нет погибших Гудермес нету ни
one I mean it turns out that
один В смысле так получается то что
Russians die
русские умирают
at funerals not
на похорона не
[laughter]
[смех]
was I can say I just ask anyone from
был могу я сказать Просто я кого из
Russia to prepare
России не спрошу пригото
[music]
[музыка]
that's how we work  you see we drink tea
вот так у нас работа видишь чай пьём
we drink coffee we work not cool listen you I will
кофе пьём работаем не классно слуша вы я
say this when I communicate with
скажу так я когда вот сколько общаюсь с
people from Russia I admire the Chechens
людьми из России Я восхищаюсь чеченцами
Yes they did something like that Russia gives a
Да они как-то так сделали Россия даёт на
lot of money to Chechnya Russians go to die in
Чечню кучу денег россияне идут умирать
short to Ukraine uh Chechnya takes a lot of
короче в Украину ээ Чечня берёт кучу
money yes but there is not a single dead
денег да но ни одного погибшего нет
Handsome Handsome
Красавчики Красавчики
Rita I don't know a lot of money I have never seen a lot of
Рите кучу денег не знаю я восне не видал
money in my dreams
кучу
Neli 76
Нели 76
sa
са
like So yes It's interesting and it
подоб Так что да Интересно а
turns out that here is inst top Kaps Akhmad Well
получается вот inst топ Капс ахмада Ну
top Kaps Akhma Just if you
топ Капс ахма Просто если есть
want go and have a look I'll go and have a
желание зайди посмот посмотрю зайду
look Yes, it's
посмотрю Да
interesting that you so advertised through
интересно это вы так рекламируется через
the summer Yes yes I have Instagram And do you
летку Да да у меня Инстаграме А
deliver to other countries at least to
доставочка в другие страны делаете хоть
any point in the world to me in Kyiv you can
любую точку мира мне в Киев можете
deliver to the guys I want to pass on Here I
доставить ребятам хочу передать Вот я
personally will deliver to me
лично пове мне доставку сделаю потому
because there are guys from the Sheikh battalion
что там есть ребята из батальона Шейха
if personally this is a joke but it is not no
если лично это шутка но так не это не
joke I have
шутка у меня
friends who give
знакомые
discounts I have friends who are Chechens and
скидки у меня знакомые чеченцы есть
who fight in the battalion  Sheikh Mansur
которые воюют в батальоне Шейха Мансура
vs. Russia Oh, I would give them some kind of cap
против России О я бы им кепочку какую-то
if it can be delivered to Kyiv, but
подогнал если в Киев можно доставить но
I don’t know if your delivery service
я не знаю ли там доставочка у вас
works there, I don’t know for sure,
работает точно не знаю
I’m where the war is there I’m not here, I’m fine here,
я где война там Меня нету я здесь хорошо
but for example, somewhere in the rear Here you are do you like
а а например куда-то в тыл Вот ты любишь
I noticed to talk about war yes yes
я вот заметил про войну поговорить да да
about war I want I have
про войну Я хочу У меня есть знакомый
another friend this bast shoes Aladin I want to
ещё один этот лапти Аладина Я хочу ему
give him a cap maybe he is somewhere there
передать кепку может можно он где-то там
personally you will give it to him not like that I am closer to you
лично ему передашь не так Я у вас заж
not here you yourself personally want come
ближе не вот ты сам лично хо приехать
here to us Aren't you afraid to come here
сюда к нам А ты не боишься сюда прийти А
Why do I need what am I looking for there He needs my
зачем мне что я там ищу Ему же нужна моя
You see, that's it, that's it, you know, eh,
Видишь вот вот вот вот это знаешь э вот
many people talk like that, such moments,
многие вот так вот такие моменты
because we are far away Yeah, That's
разговаривают потому что мы далеко Угу
it,
Вот
A,
А
approximately, to get to know yourself, there is
примерно чтобы себя узнать вот есть
examples Well, what under cover at night You
примеры Ну что под покровом ночью Ты
can
сможешь
go to the cemetery
пойти кладбище примерно
yourself, yes, I've gone more than
сам да ходил не
once, different moments, you can
раз разные моменты можно чтобы
check today This is an example Yes, I'll go
провери сегодня Это пример Да я пойду
there when it's dark
туда когда вот Темно стало
there, on the contrary, it
там наоборот
happens when What's scary in the
бывает когда А что страшного на
cemetery Well, this is just an example,
кладбище ну это пример просто пример
why is it scarier? at night in  some
поему более страшно пой ночью в какой-то
bar where there's action there's scarier than in a
бар где там движуха там страшнее чем на
treasure in a cemetery no one will
клад на кладбище никто тебя не не
stand up for you and won't do anything But in a bar you
встанет и ничего не сделает А вот в баре
can
можно
get in a bar there you can get yes yes
получить в баре там можно получить да да
And in a cemetery what In a cemetery everyone is
А на кладбище что На кладбище все
harmless Well I don't
безобидные Ну не
know you see
знаю вот видишь
people  talk politics well yes
лю политику разговаривать ну да потому
because I myself come from Rostov but as I
что я сам родом из Ростова но как бы я
see that my country Russia it kills
смотрю что моя страна Россия она убивает
people in Ukraine [ __ ] think all military
людей в Украине сри думае все военные
people all fight Yes maybe we'll
люди все воюют Да может это
leave this politics together to the politicians
политику вместе оставим политикам
and you coffee
иты кофе
sa
са
Ay guys recognized you apparently yes yes
Ай ребята узнали тебя видимо да да
recognized  found out I'm such a famous
узнали узнали я такой известный
provocateur They say you have
провокатор Говорят у вас в Инстаграме
some kind of broadcast on Instagram Yes, it
какая-то трансляция Да
's going on Yes,
идёт да
you're making interesting
Вы интересно
progress We
продвигается Мы
work like
работаем вот так
this well I'll run
вот хорошо побегу
on I'll
дальше
run on
р побегу дальше
Oh well, if there's something else to talk about
А ладно если есть что-то ещё поговорить
we can
можем ещё
talk about something else As you can see
поговорить о чём Как вы видите
Look here  I know you're not a politician yes
Смотри вот я знаю что ты не политик да
yes
да
and you still do it Well you have a blog
и всё равно занимаешься Ну у тебя блог
blog what do I do yes I keep a blog on
блог ведёшь что я да Лог веду по
politics
политике
so talk about
так про
war
войну
well you talk to people
разговаривать ну ты с людьми
yes yes their their opinion there
разговариваешь да да их ихние мнение там
with  Russians Yes, although
с россиянами Да хотя
they work there and do their own
они работает там занимается своими
thing Well, I am also a simple person and I
делами Ну я ж тоже я простой человек и
communicate with simple people Yes, it is interesting
общаюсь с простыми людьми Да интересно
Let politicians communicate with politicians And I am a
Пусть политики общаются с политиками А я
simple person communicating with simple
простой человек общаюсь с простыми
people Well, let politicians communicate with
людьми А ну пусть политики общаются с
politicians And I am a simple person I speak
политиками А я простой человек я говорю
with  ordinary people I have such you Well you
с простыми людьми у меня такая ты Ну ты
And you admit it that you are not a politician
же А ты признаёшь это что ты не политик
I am not a politician a politician is deputies
Я же не политик политик - это депутаты
presidents
президенты
you see
видишь вот
this today on the Internet there are different ones
это сегодняшнее в интернете же разные
I go there different different each in their
я захожу там разный разный каждый
own way there speaks you understand as
по-своему там говорит понимаешь как
if there  he happens and it's as if he
будто там он бывает и как будто бы он
sees everything But what do you think? As a
видит всё А вот как ты думаешь Вот как
simple person, why did this war
простой человек из-за чего эта война
start? I
началась Я
think I don't know
думаю я не знаю
where you're from You know something different I'm
откуда ты Ты знаешь примерно не так мне
interested in your opinion as a person from
интересно ваше мнение как человека из
Russia, Russia attacked. Here you are
России Россия же напала Вот вы
thought Why is it like that Well, I'm telling you
задумались Почему так Ну вот говорю тебе
I don't
Я не
know how a
знаю откуда
person can know
может человек знать
these things when here Look, I'm in the morning
эти вещи когда вот здесь Смотри я утром
approximately I'm talking after lunch I
примерно Я говорю после обеда Захожу я
come in in the evening and work until
вечером бываю и работаю до
the last minute
последнего
you know I'm such a person if I haven't
знаешь я вот такой человек если я не
seen if I haven't seen I  I won't say that
видел вот если я не видел я не буду это
Yeah, spread it all
Угу распространять тем
the more so,
более вот
and who do you think Crimea is? How do you
а как вы считаете чей Крым вы как
make a living? I'm a
зарабатываете на жизнь примерно я
programmer. Well, you kind of have time. Yes,
программист Ну вы как бы успеваете Да
I work here. I work with my fingers and
работать здесь я работаю пальцами и
brains. And in the evenings, I work
мозгами а вечером работаю
here for a few hours. Yes, for a
здесь ну по несколько часов ведёте Да по
few hours. Yes, the American
несколько часов Да мне американский
State Department pays me.  salary now
госдеп платит зарплату сейчас из-за того
because Trump came there for 90 days
что там Трамп немножко пришёл на 90 дней
they are delaying YouTube YouTube pays Yes not
задерживают YouTube YouTube платит Да не
directly Americans
прямо американцы напрямую
pay directly yes
платят да
yes for the fact that I find people from the
да за то что я нахожу людей из
Russian Federation and
Российской Федерации и
implement the book instruction
внедряют книжку инструкцию
they passed on so that they show Okay
передали прот чтобы те показа Окей
Okay book Janusz  bugayskiy instructions on
О'кей книга Януш бугайский инструкция с
dismemberment of Russia here is an American
расчленения России вот американский
towel written very by the way I
рушник написал очень кстати я тут про
read about Chechnya here Very also Interesting you are Russian
Чечню читал Очень тоже Интере ты русские
and Russian Yes I am not Russian I am from the city of
а русский Да я не русский Я из города
Khmelnitsky Ukraine this is my Legend
Хмельницкий Украина это у меня Легенда
that I am from America that I am from Russia and so
что я из Америки что я из России и так
on Yes yes I was joking  you were joking but you weren't joking
дальше Да да шутил шутил ты да не шутил
but specifically to
а специально
infiltrate as an Agent to infiltrate into
внедряться как Агент внедряться в
Trust in people
Доверие людям
that's my job that's my job
вот у меня работа такая это моя работа у
someone else's job is to go kill people in
кого-то работа идти убивать людей в
Ukraine that's my job
Украину у меня такая
work
работа
yes yes yes So I don't know as they say
дадада Так что я не знаю как говорится
To each his own, everyone will find their own at the end of the
Каждому своё каждый найдёт своё в конце
road and we will all answer there before
пути да и все будем отвечать там перед
the Almighty
всевышним
Yes of course no problem We are all
Да конечно без проблем Мы все люди
mortal people someone will die true
смертные кто-то умрёт правда
sooner someone
быстрее кто-то
later yes Okay I will continue to go on let's go
позже да Хорошо буду и дальше идти давай
Salam he was upset that I was from Ukraine,
Салам он расстроился что я из Украины
of course a shocking guy,
эпатажный конечно тип
I thought it was
я блин думал это
some kind of Sheriff, a real Chechen
какой-то Шериф реально чеченец
from I have a friend, Akhmet Izr, so like,
из У меня друг есть Ахмет изр так лайк
subscribe, come on, subscribe to
подписка комен донн подпишись на й
Telegram right now, axis VN,
Telegram прям зараз ось ВН
apok, this is very and very important, YouTube is busy
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
with us through  skarg ORV your ban and very
нас через скарг ОРВ твый бан и дуже
many videos do not show people at times do not
багато видео не показуе людям вчасно не
show information about streams To that so
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
that we Mali operational links
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
are written right now and while there in telegram
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okm video there is also interesting and useful
окм видео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we are sorry for you constant
информация и ми повинни з вами тримати
posting  operational linkage
постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that che will show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine letter
YouTube Слава Украине пись
with
с